A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.29 (A2003) FA490
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2003.063: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2001; AC.2003.063; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3581, R3582.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.063.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 94021 #9 - UNIVERSITE NATIONALE DE COTE D'IVOIRE (IVORY COAST) - CONTROL OF AFRICAN CASSAVA MOSAIC VIRUS, 1994-2001 (Box R3582)
- AC.2003.066: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2004; AC.2003.066; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3583-R3586.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.066.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 94022 #4 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR EDWARD ORONY-OMOLO, 1996-2001 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94024 #89 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SAN FRANCISCO) - PREVENTION OF MOTHER TO CHILD TRANSMISSION OF HIV-1 IN NORTHERN THAILAND, 1994-1998 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94025 #19 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN MOLECULAR ASPECTS OF REPRODUCTION, 1993-2000 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94025 #27 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - WOMEN'S PREFERENCES FOR CONTRACEPTIVE TECHNOLOGY, 1995-2000; 2004 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94027 #602 - AMBALI, AGGREY J.D. - ACA: "GENETIC IMPROVEMENT AND CONSERVATION OF BIODIVERSITY RELEVANT TO AQUACULTURE IN MALAWI", 1996-1999 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94027 #604 - ANZALA, AGGREY OMU - ACA: "LONG-TERM NONPROGRESSIVE HIV-1 INFECTION", 1996-2000 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94027 #623 - BERISSO, TADDESSE - ACA: "ETHIOPIA'S AGRICULTURAL POLICY ANALYSIS", 1996-2002 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94027 #624 - MOYO, NGONIDZASHE - ACA: "BIOLOGICAL CONTROL OF SNAIL INTERMEDIATE HOSTS OF SCHISTOSOMIASIS BY SARGOCHROMIS CODRINGTONI IN ZIMBABWE", 1996-2000 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94027 #629 - TARHULE, AONDOVER AUGUSTINE - ACA: "GROUND-WATER RECHARGE FROM SEASONAL STREAM IN SEMI-ARID NIGERIA", 1996-2002 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94033 #105 - BELCHER, BRIAN MURRAY - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1996-1999 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94038 #13 - INDIA FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1993-2002 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94043 #209 - BRAVA FOR WOMEN IN THE ARTS - LOOKING FOR BAYARD, 1991-2002 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94050 - (AGROFORESTRY) - CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1997 (Box R3583)
    - RF 94054 #27 - INTERNATIONAL PROJECTS ASSISTANCE SERVICES - FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES FOR WOMEN TREATED FOR ABORTION COMPLICATIONS IN ZIMBABWE, 1995-2002 (Box R3584)
    - RF 94054 #31 - RURAL WOMEN'S SOCIAL EDUCATION CENTRE (INDIA) - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH PROGRAM AND DEVELOP INDICATORS FOR REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICES, 1995-2001 (Box R3584)
    - RF 94055 #19 - JAMAICA PUBLIC SERVICE COMPANY, LTD. - COGENERATION PROJECTS TECHNICAL AND ECONOMIC FEASIBILITY, 1995-2000 (Box R3584)
    - RF 94064 - MINORITY-FOCUSED POLICY ANALYSIS CENTERS, 1994-1997 (Box R3584)
    - RF 94064 - MINORITY-FOCUSED POLICY ANALYSIS CENTERS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1997 (Box R3584)
    - RF 95001 #334 - TEXAS A, 1994-2001 (Box R3584)
    - RF 95001 #338 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - MANAGEMENT OF RICE SHEATH BLIGHT, 1994-1999 (Box R3585)
    - RF 95001 #356 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - APPLICATION OF BIOTECHNOLOGY TO GENETIC IMPROVEMENT OF RICE, 1989-1999 (Box R3585)
    - RF 95001 #368 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - RICE INSECT RESISTANCE GENES, 1995-1999 (Box R3585)
    - RF 95001 #379 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (IND/A) - NOVEL BT STRAINS AND ANALYSIS OF CRY PROTEINS FELLOWSHIP, 1995-2000 (Box R3585)
    - RF 95007 #62 -EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - PHOSTATE FERTILIZERS AND MAIZE IN THE SIAYA DISTRICT, 1995-2001 (Box R3585)
    - RF 95010 #55 - AMERICAN ACADEMY OF ARTS AND SCIENCES - ENVIRONMENTAL SCARCITY, 1993-2001 (Box R3585)
    - RF 95010 #76 - GHANA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - FAMILY PLANNING IN RURAL GHANA, 1995-1999 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95011 - PARIVAR SEVA SANSTHA (INDIA) - RESEARCH TO IMPROVE REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICE DELIVERY, 1994-2001 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95019 #14 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - SORGHUM GENOME ANALYSIS, 1995-2001 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95020 #104 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - VITAMIN A AND PERINATAL HIV TRANSMISSION IN ZIMBABWE, 1996-1999 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95020 #106 - UNIVERSITY OF MANITOBA (CANADA) - GENETIC AND PHENOTYPIC CHARACTERIZATION OF RESISTANCE TO HIV-1 INFECTION, 1996 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95021 #35 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA - INSTITUTE OF PRIMATE RESEARCH - CONTRACEPTIVE-21 INITIATIVE, 1995-1998 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95021 #36 - ZHEJIANG ACADEMY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES (CHINA) - CLINICAL PHARMACOLOGY OF CONTRACEPTION, 1995-1999 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #644 - DJAMBA, YANYI K. - ACA: KINSHIP SYSTEM AND FERTILITY BEHAVIOR IN RURAL ZAIRE, 1996-2002 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #645 - ESELE, PETER J. - ACA: DISEASE FUNGUS PYRICULARIA GRISEA, 1996-2001 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #649 - ADOMAKO, JOSEPHINE A. - ADIA: "GENDER IN EQUALITIES, POWER IN UNIONS AND REPRODUCTIVE DECISION-MAKING IN GHANA", 1997-2002 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #658 - EKWAMU, ADIPALA - ACA: FARMER-FRIENDLY PRATICES AGAINST LATE BLIGHT OF POTATO IN UGANDA, 1997-2001 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #672 - TRE, JEAN-PHILIPPE - ALTERNATIVE BIOMASS MANAGEMENT FOR PERENNIAL PLANTAIN IN NIGERIA, 1997-1999 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #674 - FADLALLA, AMAL HASSAN - ADIA: WOMEN'S STRATEGIES AND RITUALS OF FERTILITY AMONG HADENDOWA OF EASTERN SUDAN, 1997-2000 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #677 - SALO, ELAINE - ADIA: "NEGOTIATING ADOLESCENCE AND SEXUALITY IN KHAYELITSHA, SOUTH AFRICA", 1996-2000 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #679 - OMBAKHO, GEORGE ANTHONY - ACA: MAIZE IN KENYA, 1996-2002 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #682 - MUGO, FRIDAN - ADIA: TREE PLANTING AND FUELWOOD AVAILABILITY IN KENYA, 1997-2000 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #684 - OGBECHIE, SYLVESTER - ADIA: IDEOLOGY OF FORM IN TWENTIETH-CENTURY NIGERIAN ART, 1997-2002 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #689 - SHILARO, PRISCILLA M. - ADIA: "BRITISH TURSTEESHIP, AFRICAN LAND RIGHTS AND KAKAMEGA GOLD RUSH 1930-1953", 1997-2002 (Box R3586)
    - RF 95022 #695 - KEBEDE, DEREGE - ACA: MENTAL AND BEHAVIORAL DISORDERS AMONG RURAL CHILDREN IN ETHIOPIA, 1997-2000 (Box R3586)
- AC.2003.072: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2003.072; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3587-R3592.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.072.1; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - RF 94033 #106; RF 95038 #107 - EDMUNDS, DAVID STUARTSOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1997-2002 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95022 #699 - MBAJEKWE, PATRICKADIA: LAND AND URBAN DEVELOPMENT IN ONITSHA, NIGERIA, 1900-1990s, 1997-1999 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95022 #702 - THEMELI, BOOI - ADIA: "PRIVATIZATION AND LABOR MARKETS IN SOUTH AFRICA", 1997-1999 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95022 #704 - CHIMEDZA, ROBERTADIA: DEAF STUDENTS IN ZIMBABWE, 1997-1999 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95023 #38 - JERUSALEM INTERNATIONAL BOOK FAIR (ISRAEL) - 18TH BIENNIAL BOOK FAIR, 1996-1999 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95024 #260 - CROSSPULSE - MUSIC AND DANCE COLLABORATION, "PERAYAAN/THE CELEBRATION", 1996-2000 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95037 #7 - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA (CHARLOTTESVILLE) - NON-HOST RESISTANCE IN MAIZE TO INFECTION, 1996-1999 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95038 #108 - JOHNSON, NANCY LEIGHSOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1997-2001 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95038 #109 - OTIENO, JOSEPH OLUOCH - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1997-2001 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95038 #110 - EDMONDS, CHRISTOPHER MICHAELSOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1997-2001 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95040 #72 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT AND ENVIRONMENTAL CONSERVATION IN ZANZIBAR - SCIENCE EDUCATION CENTER, 1996-2002 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95046 #13 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - PAPAYA BIOTECHNOLOGY NETWORK OF SOUTHEAST ASIA, 1998-2000 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95046 #13 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - PAPAYA BIOTECHNOLOGY NETWORK OF SOUTHEAST ASIA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2000 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95046 #15 - STOCKHOLM ENVIRONMENT INSTITUTE {SWEDEN)WORKSHOP ON TRANSGENIC ORGANISMS DIFFUSION, 1997-2000 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95046 #16 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS, 1998-2002 (Box R3587)
    - RF 95050 #107 - YEBOAH, VIDA AMAADI - INFLUENCE OF SOCIO-CULTURAL FACTORS ON GIRLS' ENROLLMENT IN SCIENCE AT SECONDARY SCHOOL IN GHANA, 1996-2002 (Box R3588)
    - RF 95059 #99 - UWAMEIYE, RAYMOND - ACHIEVEMENT OF FEMALE STUDENTS IN INTRODUCTORY TECHNOLOGY COURSES IN NIGERIA, 1996-2002 (Box R3588)
    - RF 95051 - DEVELOPMENT OF PHILANTHROPY ABROAD, 1993-1999 (Box R3588)
    - RF 95051 #15 - OAXACA COMMUNITY FOUNDATION (MEXICO) - GENDER AND SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY PROGRAMS, 1998-2000 (Box R3588)
    - RF 95053 - UNDERSTANDING THEORIES OF CIVIL SOCIETY, 1995 (Box R3588)
    - RF 95054 #37 - CENTER FOR ARTS CRITICISM - "SISTERS IN LEADERSHIP", 1997-2000 (Box R3588)
    - RF 95054 #41 - WING LUKE MEMORIAL FOUNDATION - REFLECTIONS OF ASIAN - PACIFIC AMERICAN VETERANS, 1997-2000 (Box R3589)
    - RF 95064 - FOUNDATION CENTER, 1969-1998 (Box R3589)
    - RF 95064 - FOUNDATION CENTER - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1969-1998 (Box R3589)
    - RF 96001 #412 - TEXAS A M UNIVERSITY - TEXAS AGRICULTURAL EXPERIMENT STATION - ALIEN GENE TRANSFER IN RICE, 1995-1998 (Box R3589)
    - RF 96001 #414 - SRI LANKA - AGRICULTURE (DEPT OF) - RICE RESEARCH DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE - GALL MIDGE RESISTANT RICE, 1995-2000 (Box R3589)
    - RF 96001 #420 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - RICE BLAST FUNGUS MAGNAPORTE GRISEA, 1996-1999 (Box R3589)
    - RF 96001 #424 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - MITOCHONDRIAL DNA IN RICE, 1990-2000 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96001 #435 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - ROOT MORPHOLOGY OF RICE, 1995-1999 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96001 #468 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE VARIETIES RESISTANT TO FUNGAL DISEASE, 1996-2003 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96001 #471 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MOLECULAR MARKER-ASSISTED BREEDING AND RICE, 1996-1999 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96001 #478 - NANJING AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR HE CHENYANG, 1996-1999 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96001 #482 - ORISSA UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE AND TECHNOLOGY - WIDE HYBRIDIZATION FOR RICE IMPROVEMENT, 1991-1999 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96001 #486 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (DAVIS) - MAINTENANCE AND DISTRIBUTION OF A RICE BACTERIAL ARTIFICIAL CHROMOSOME (SAC) LIBRARY, 1992-1999 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96005 #106 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - SOIL FERTILITY AND MOISTURE IN SANDY SOILS, 1996-2001 (Box R3590)
    - RF 96006 #11 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - STRIGA RESISTANCE IN AFRICAN MAIZE, 1996-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96006 #12 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - STRIGA CONTROL AND AFRICAN MAIZE RESISTANCE, 1996-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96007 #22 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY - GENETIC BIODIVERSITY IN BANANA WEEVIL, 1996-1999 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96010 #22 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - COLLABORATIVE STUDY OF CASSAVA IN AFRICA (COSCA), 1992-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96015 #147 - MUSEUM OF CHINESE IN THE AMERICAS - EXHIBITIONS AND PUBLICATIONS ON CHINESE-AMERICAN COMMUNITY IN SUNSET PARK, BROOKLYN, 1995-1999 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96020 #53 - MOUNT SINAI SCHOOL OF MEDICINE - MAMMALIAN EGG AND SPERM ADHESION MOLECULES (CANCELLED), 1996-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96020 #58 - IHF INSTITUTE FOR HORMONE AND FERTILITY RESEARCH (GERMANY) - EPIDIDYMIS-SPECIFIC GENES AS CONTRACEPTIVE TARGETS (RESCINDED), 1996-1999 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #709 - GOGA, SORAYA E. - AIDA: "TOWARDS EQUITY? PROPERTY DEVELOPMENT AND POST APARTHEID CITY", 1997-2002 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #717 - NGWENYA, BARBARA NTOMBI - ADIA: GENDER AND SOCIAL TRANSFORMATI ON IN BOTSWANA, 1997-2002 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #719 - PARIYO, GEORGE WILLIAM - ADIA: PUBLIC RESOURCES IN DECENTRALIZED HEALTH SYSTEMS IN UGANDA, 1997-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #726 - MALUWA-BANDA, DIXIE - ADIA: ADOLESCENT SEXUALITY AND HIV/AIDS IN MALAWI, 1997-2002 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #728 - MUGENDI, DANIEL NJIRU - ACA: AGRO-FORESTRY TECHNOLOGIES TO SUPPORT CROP PRODUCTION IN KENYA, 1997-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #734 - MPOFU, ELIAS - ADIA: SOCIAL ACCEPTANCE OF ZIMBABWEAN EARLY ADOLESCENTS WITH PHYSICAL DISABILITIES, 1997-1999 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #741 - NKIWANE, TANDEKA CHARMAINE - ADIA: POLITICAL ELITES AND REGIONAL SECURITY IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1997-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #743 - WONG, MADELEINE - ADIA: TRANSNATIONAL MOVEMENTS, MIGRANT REMITTANCES AND DEVELOPMENT IN GHANA, 1998-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #745 - GNOUMOU, BRIGITTE - ADIA: CATTLE AND MANURE MANAGEMENT TO INCREASE SOIL FERTILITY IN NIGER, 1998-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #747 - FARR, VANESSA - ADIA: BLACK WOMEN'S LIFE WRITING IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1997-1999 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #749 - SHEIKH, DEKHA - ADIA: IMPACT OF LIVESTOCK TECHNOLOGIES ON HOUSEHOLD WELFARE, 1998-2002 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #753 - KIHANDA, FRANCIS MUCHOKI - ACA: FARMYARD MANURE QUALITY THROUGH COMPOSTING WITH ORGANIC RESIDUES, 1998-2000 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #761 - KABEERE, FLAVIA - ACA: HOME-SAVED SEED QUALITY IN UGANDA, 1997-1999 (Box R3591)
    - RF 96022 #764 - HANSON, KOBENA TSETSE - ADIA: ECONOMIC RESTRUCTURING IN MATRILINEAL URBAN GHANA, 1998-2002 (Box R3591)
    - EO 9736; RF 96026 #19 - CALIFORNIA INSTITUTE FOR EFFECTIVE ACTION - ECONOMIC CONDITIONS IN SAN DIEGO; CONSULT ON ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1997-2001 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96022 #766 - KILLLIAN, BERNADETA - ADIA: CULTURAL CHANGE IN KENYA, 1998-2000 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96022 #769 - SAUTE, ALDA ROMANO - ADIA: AFRICAN-MISSION ENCOUNTER AND EDUCATION IN MOZAMBIQUE, 1998-2000 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96022 #771 - MUSIIWA, STELLA - ADIA: SMALLHOLDER IRRIGATION TECHNOLOGY IN MANICALAND, 1928-1997, 1998-2000 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96022 #777 - LEKGOATHI, SEKIBAKIBA PETER - ADIA: SOUTH AFRICAN CHIEFDOM: ZEBEDIELA C., 1830-1994, 1998-2000 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96022 #793 - CAMARA, ALPHA OUMAR - ACA: HEALTH STATUS OF CHILDREN IN A RURAL COMMUNITY OF GUINEA, AFRICA, 1996-2000 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96023 #249 - BITOMSKY, HARTMUT - DOCUMENTARY, "B-52", 1997-2004 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96023 #251 - JENIK, ADRIENE - INTERACTIVE WEB SITE, "P.O.S. WORLD", 1997-2002 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96026 #18 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - COMPETITIVE ALTERNATIVES IN SERVICE DELIVERY INITIATIVE, 1996-2000 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96026 #24 - ALAMEDA COUNTY - INTERAGENCY CHILDREN'S POLICY COUNCIL - EMPLOYMENT STRATEGIES AND NEIGHBORHOOD FAMILY SUPPORT SERVICES, 1995-1998; 2003 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96030 - INDEPENDENT SECTOR - PUBLIC AWARENESS OF INDEPENDENT SECTOR IN AMERICAN LIFE, 1996-1998 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96031 - TASK FORCE FOR CHILD SURVIVAL DEVELOPMENT, 1996-1998 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96032 - WORLD BANK - GLOBAL DISEASE-CONTROL AND VACCINES, 1996 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96035 #503 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY RESOURCE AND TRAINING CENTER, 1986-1997 (Box R3592)
    - RF 96035 #503 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY RESOURCE AND TRAINING CENTER - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1986-1997 (Box R3592)
- AC.2003.073: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2003; AC.2003.073; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3593-R3594.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.073.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 96036 #56 - MCMASTER UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - WORKSHOP ON PROBLEM BASED LEARNING METHODOLOGY IN UGANDA, 1997-1998 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96040 #50 - INTERNATIONAL AFRICAN INSTITUTE (ENGLAND) - CONFERENCES ON AFRICAN CULTURAL COOPERATION AND DEVELOPMENT, 1997-1999 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96040 #51 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - 1998 AFRICAN FILM FESTIVAL, 1997-1999 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96040 #52 - 18TH STREET ARTS COMPLEX - RESIDENCIES FOR AFRICAN ARTISTS, 1997-1999 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96040 #54 - INTERNATIONAL MUSIC COUNCIL (FRANCE) - NETWORKING BETWEEN NATIONAL MUSIC ASSOCIATIONS IN AFRICA, 1997-1999 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96040 #57 - COUNCIL FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH IN AFRICA (CODESRIA) - WORKSHOPS ON CONTEMPORARY AFRICAN CULTURAL HISTORY, 1997-2001 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96041 #50 - LAWYERS COMMITTEE FOR HUMAN RIGHTS - DISSEMINATION OF REPORTS ON ISLAMIC ISSUES, 1996-1999 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96041 #52 - ASHTAR FOR THEATRE PRODUCTIONS AND TRAINING (ISRAEL) - "ABU SHAKER'S AFFAIR '98", 1998 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96047 #96 - UNION DE EJIDOS Y COMUNIDADES DE CAFETICULTORES DEL BENEFICIO MAJOMUT (MEXICO) - COFFEE CULTIVATION IN LOS ALTOS DE CHIAPAS, 1993-2000 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96047 #97 - AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - AGRO ECOLOGY PROGRAM, 1996-2003 (Box R3593)
    - RF 96047 #101 - EL COLEGIO DE LA FRONTERA SUR (MEXICO) - MAIZE-LEGUME SYSTEMS IN CHIAPAS, 1993-2003 (Box R3594)
    - RF 96047 #104 - LINEA BIOSFERA (MEXICO) - GMCC SYSTEMS ASSESSMENT AND SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE, 1996-2003 (Box R3594)
    - RF 96047 #105 - GRUPO INTERDISCIPLINARIO DE TECHNOLOGIA RURAL APROPIADA (GIRA) A.G. - (MEXICO) - STRENGTHEN THE NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT PROGRAM IN MEXICO, 1994-2000 (Box R3594)
    - RF 96047 #98 - PROGRAM FOR THE INTEGRAL USE OF NATURAL RESOURCES (MEXICO) - SUSTAINABLE MANAGEMENT OF NATURAL RESOURCES IN SAN NICOLAS ZOYATLAN, 1998-2000 (Box R3594)
    - RF 96047 #99 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT OF THE TUXLAS (MEXICO) - IMPROVED FARMING OF MAIZE SYSTEMS IN VERACRUZ, 1995-2001 (Box R3594)
- AC.2003.087: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2003.087; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes, R3595-R3601.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.087.1; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - AH 9802; RF 96058 #109 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - INFORMATION AND CONVENING SERVICES OF ARTS INTERNATIONAL AND INROADS/THE AMERICAS FESTIVAL, 1997-1999 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96048 #59 - BURKINA FASO - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - COLLECT DATA ON ABORTION AND PREGNANCY IN BAZEGA PROVINCE, 1998-2000 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96051 #117 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF SCIENTIFIC UNIONS (FRANCE) - WORKSHOP ON DEVELOPING GENDER-SENSITIVE POPULAR READING MATERIAL, 1997-1999 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96055 #2 - OLDENBURG UNIVERSITY (GERMANY) - ACTIVITIES RELATED TO LEGACY OF ABSENCE HOLOCAUST EXHIBITION, 1998-1999 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96056 #4 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - ROLE OF ARTS AND CULTURE IN COMMUNITY-BUILDING, 1997-2004 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96056 #7 - UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO - STUDY OF ARTS PROGRAMS FOR CHILDREN AND YOUTH IN CHICAGO, 1997-1999 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96057 #43 - SAN DIEGO REPERTORY THEATRE - PERFORMANCES AND EXHIBITS, "MID-CITY IN CALAFIA", 1997-1999 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96057 #44 - COALITION FOR IMMIGRANT AND REFUGEE RIGHTS AND SERVICES - ''TRANSFORMING INSTITUTIONS" PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96057 #49 - APPALSHOP - CONVENING PACT GRANTEES ON ART AND SOCIAL CHANGE, 1998-2003 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96058 #110 - CONTEMPORARY AMERICAN THEATRE FESTIVAL - "CARRY THE TIGER TO THE MOUNTAIN", 1998-1999 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96065 - COMMON ENTERPRISE, 1993-2000 (Box R3595)
    - RF 96065 - COMMON ENTERPRISE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2000 (Box R3595, Box R3596)
    - RF 96066 #1 - OMMUNITY PARTNERSHIP DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION - EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES FOR TENANTS IN CITY-OWNED HOUSING, 1994-1999 (Box R3596)
    - RF 97001 #516 - OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY - RECEPTOR BINDING OF VARIOUS ENDOTOXINS TO BORERS MIDGUTS, 1992-2000 (Box R3596)
    - RF 97001 #524 - LEHMAN COLLEGE - IMPROVEMENT OF RICE ENDOSPERM CAROTENOID CONTENT, 1992-1999 (Box R3597)
    - RF 97001 #525 - CENTER FOR THE APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE (CAMBIA) (AUSTRALIA) - DISSEMINATION TECHNIQUES FOR RICE TRANSGENESIS AND MOLECULAR BIOLOGY, 1993-1999 (Box R3597)
    - RF 97001 #529 - TATA INSTITUTE OF FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - MOLECULAR BIOLOGY AND TRANSFORMATION OF RICE, 1995-2002 (Box R3597)
    - RF 97001 #533 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE - CLONING GENES FROM ARABADOPSIS THALIANA AND ORYZA SATIVA, 1990-2000 (Box R3597)
    - RF 97001 #535 - OSMANIA UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR K. VENKATESWARA RAO, 1996-1999 (Box R3597)
    - RF 97001 #536 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR VIJAY CHOWDHURY, 1996-2000 (Box R3597)
    - RF 97001 #537 - ZHEJIANG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA} - SOIL RELATED STRESSES OF RICE, 1994-2002 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #564 - SCRIPPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - ESTABLISH A RICE TRANSFORMATION TRAINING CENTER, 1994-2002 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #567 - LA TUAN NGHIA - DISSERTATION FELLOWSHIP IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1997-1999 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #569 - RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR HATHAIRAT URAIRONG, 1996-2001 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #580 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - TRANSGENIC RICE PLANTS, 1990-2002 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #582 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - GENETIC MANIPULATION OF ANTIFUNGAL SUBTANCES FROM BACTERIA, 1992-2002 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #584 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - RICE YELLOW STUNT VIRUS, 1990-2002 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #589 - SHANDONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - EFFICIENT RICE TRANSFORMATION AND RESISTANCE TO INSECTS, 1993-2002 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #592 - KING MONGKUT'S INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY LADKRABANG (THAILAND) - THAI RICE GENETIC TRANSFORMATION BY AGROBACTERIUM, 1997-2000 (Box R3598)
    - RF 97001 #599 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - FIELD TEST OF TRANSGENIC RICE IN CHINA, 1997-2000 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97002 #127 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - WORKSHOP ON POST-DIAGNOSTIC METHODOLOGY AND FARMER PARTICIPATION, 1997-1999 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97002 #130 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT AND REGIONAL RESEARCH PROGRAM, 1997-2001 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97002 #143 - ROTHAMSTED EXPERIMENTAL STATION (ENGLAND) - LONG-TERM AGRONOMIC TRIALS IN AFRICA, 1996-2000 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97003 #23 - ENTRE FOR AGRICULTURE AND BIOSCIENCES INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - SURVEY OF STORAGE INSECT PESTS IN KENYA, 1997-1998 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97005 #109 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRJCULTURE - NEMATODE POPULATION AND MAIZE, 1998-2002 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97006 - RESEARCH FELLOWSHIPS IN THE AGRJCULTURAL SCIENCES, 1991-1998 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97006 #27 - DEVRIES, JOSEPH - MAIZE BREEDING RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP, 1996-2002 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97007 #27 - SCRIPPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF CASSAVA FOR VIRUS RESISTANCE, 1991-1999 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97007 #27 - Scripps Research Institute - Genetic Engineering of Cassava for Virus Resistance - Supplementary Material, 1991-1999 (Box R3599)
    - RF 97009 - TRANSITION TO A NEW ENERGY PARADIGM, 1994-2000 (Box R3599, Box R3600)
    - RF 97009 - TRANSITION TO A NEW ENERGY PARADIGM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-2000 (Box R3599, Box R3600)
    - RF 97009 #11 - TRANSITION TO A NEW ENERGY PARADIGM - OCEAN THERMAL ENERGY CONVERSION TECHNOLOGY, 1998-1999 (Box R3600)
    - RF 97009 #12 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE ON PLANT OIL FEASIBILITY, 1997-1999 (Box R3600)
    - RF 97012 #128 - CENTER FOR CULTURAL AND TECHNICAL INTERCHANGE BETWEEN EAST AND WEST - FORUM ON MACRO-ECONOMICS AND POPULATION MOMENTUM, 1997-2000 (Box R3600)
    - RF 97012 #138 - POPULATION COUNCIL - HIGH FERTILITY AND CHILDREN'S EDUCATION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1994-2000 (Box R3600)
    - RF 97012 #140 - POPULATION COUNCIL - UNMET NEED FOR FAMILY PLANNING IN AFRICA AND ASIA, 1994-2000 (Box R3600)